in this lecture to get the bars and text
在这堂课中获取条形图和文本
aligned we will look at different
保持一致，我们将看到不同的
alignment methods I will hide the legs
对齐方法我会把腿藏起来
and show the sketch I create a new layer
并显示我创建了一个新层的草图
and call it upper body I zoom in on the
我把它叫做上半身我把它放大
first bar I select the rectangle tool I
第一个栏我选择矩形工具
drag over the first bar to match the
将鼠标拖到第一个条上以匹配
width I press the space bar a technique
我按下空格键是一种技巧
to align and duplicate at the same time
同时对齐和复制
is found in the snapping menu I activate
在我激活的捕捉菜单中找到
snapping I open the menu and Below
我打开菜单和下面的快门
alignment I activate same distances at
路线I在相同距离处激活
the bottom I click on reset to simple
在底部，我点击Reset to Simple
snapping if I want to go back I click on
抓拍如果我想回去，我点击
advanced mode we see there are now only
我们现在看到的高级模式只有
three snapping options I can snap to
我可以捕捉到的三个捕捉选项
bounding boxes which is the dotted line
作为虚线的边框
we see around the rectangle and I can
我们可以看到长方形周围，我可以
snap to nodes which I will deactivate
捕捉到我将停用的节点
together with bounding boxes what I want
加上我想要的包围盒
is to align so I will activate it if I
就是对齐，这样我就会激活它
drag the rectangle wherever I press the
将矩形拖到我按下的任何位置
space bar I will create a copy of it
空格键：我将创建它的副本
I want this rectangle to stay here so I
我想把这个长方形留在这里，这样我
press Ctrl D when I drag to the right I
当我向右拖动时按Ctrl D
see the duplicate will align to the
请参见复制件将与
original so I don't have to press Ctrl
原创，所以我不需要按Ctrl键
when I reach the second graph I press
当我到达第二个图形时，我按下
the space bar I drag further to the
我将空格键进一步拖动到
third graph inkscape is now recognizing
第三图Inkscape现在正在识别
a pattern we see an alignment line in
我们在其中看到一条对齐线的图案
the middle and a distribute line at the
中间和一条配线在
bottom
底部
so two things are happening at the same
因此，两件事同时发生
time aligning and distributing all I do
时间的排列和分配我所做的一切
is drag and press the space bar when the
是拖动并按下空格键
distribute sign appears the rectangles
分配标志出现在矩形上
have now equal distances between them
现在它们之间的距离相等
but because I am using the drawing my
而是因为我在用我的画
bars do not align perfectly with the
条形图不能与
sketch so I will reposition the last bar
素描，这样我就可以重新定位最后一根杆了
and press Ctrl a to select all bars I
并按Ctrl a选择所有栏i
open the Align and distribute panel to
打开对齐并分布面板以
redistribute the bars I click below
重新分配我在下面单击的栏
distribute uneven horizontal gaps now
现在分布不均匀的水平间隙
the bars are perfectly aligned to the
这些条完全对齐了
sketch I will drag them out I don't need
素描我会把它们拖出来我不需要
the rectangles to be a live shape so I
长方形是一个活生生的形状，所以我
will remove their own shape control
将移除它们自己的形状控件
widgets I will position the bars
小工具我将定位条形图
I press Ctrl a to select all bars I
I按Ctrl a选择所有栏i
right click and choose set clip group
右键单击并选择设置剪贴组
I select blue and bicycle kick and
我选择了蓝色和自行车腿，然后
duplicate them
复制它们
I drag the duplicates on the clip group
我拖动剪辑组上的副本
folder I will hide the sketch and show
文件夹我将隐藏草图并显示
the legs
他的腿
I also need darker bars at the bottom so
我还需要底部有深色的栏杆，所以
I duplicate the clip folder I call the
我复制了我称为
group dark bars I drag the group on the
组合深色条我将组合拖到
layer so they get on top I select the
层以使它们位于顶部，我选择
rectangles and make them black
矩形，并将其设置为黑色
I select the group folder I set the
我选择我设置的组文件夹
opacity of the folder to 60 percent I
将文件夹的不透明度提高到60%
show sketch to be able to select the
显示草图以能够选择
dark bars in the canvas I double click
我双击画布上的深色条
on a bar now I'm inside the dark bars
在酒吧里，我现在在黑暗的酒吧里
group I click on a bar and drag it down
组I单击条形图并将其向下拖动
I will also do this for the other bars
我也会为其他酒吧这么做
I hide the sketch again
我又把素描藏起来了
now I will place the text I create a new
现在我将放置我创建的新文本
layer and call it text I click on the
层，并将其称为文本我单击
text tool when I click I see a blinking
文本工具当我单击时，我看到一个闪烁
cursor for my font I choose pathway
我的字体的光标我选择路径
Gothic 1 which is a free Google font I
哥特式1，这是一个免费的谷歌字体i
will set text alignment to Center
将文本对齐设置为居中
aligned I type 81 I click on white to
已对齐我键入81，然后单击白色
make the text white I can size the text
将文本设置为白色我可以调整文本大小
by using the menu I can also size text
通过使用菜单，我还可以调整文本大小
with the select tool I hold shift plus
使用选择工具时，我按住Shift+
control and drag I want the percent sign
按住Ctrl键并拖动我需要百分号
to be smaller so I select it and make it
为了更小，所以我选择了它并制作了它
18 point I click on spacing and inside
18点，我点击间隔和内侧
vertical kerning with my up and down
上下垂直字距调整
arrows I can position the glyph you can
箭头我可以确定字形的位置
also do this on the canvas if I hold alt
如果我按住Alt键，也可以在画布上执行此操作
I can move the glyph up and down in
我可以在里面上下移动字形
small steps and I can turn the glyph so
每走一小步，我就可以把这个象形文字
move it closer a further away from the
把它移得更近一点，远离
number by holding alt and pressing the
按住Alt键并按下
left and right keys I want to repeat
我想重复一下左键和右键
this text on the other bars and I want
其他栏上的文字和我想要的
them to have the same distance to the
它们与地球上的
top of a bar to do this I will use a
要执行此操作，我将使用
placeholder I click on the rectangle
占位符：我点击该矩形
tool and enable snapping I activate node
工具并在激活节点时启用捕捉
snapping I drag a rectangle and make it
捕捉我拖动一个矩形并使其成为
Orange
桔黄色的
I place the rectangle below the text I
我把这个矩形放在文本I的下方
shift-click on the text
按住Shift键并单击文本
in align and distribute I choose
在对齐和分布中，我选择
relative to biggest object and click on
相对于最大对象并单击
Center on vertical axis now I will group
现在以垂直轴居中，我将分组
them then I duplicate the group
然后我复制这个群
for snapping I only want the corners to
对于抓拍，我只想让角落
snap so I click on advanced mode and
捕捉，因此我单击高级模式，然后
deselect bounding boxes and other points
取消选择边界框和其他点
I only want cusp nodes which means
我只想要尖点节点，这意味着
Corner nodes to snap now I drag and will
要捕捉的角结点现在我拖动并将
not let go of the mouse until all copies
在复制所有副本之前不要松开鼠标
are placed I drag to the top of the next
放在我拖到下一个顶部的位置
bar where it will snap as said I will
它会像我说的那样折断的酒吧
not let go of the mouse but press the
不是松开鼠标而是按下
space bar to place a copy
按空格键放置副本
I repeat this to create the other copies
我重复此操作以创建其他副本
now I click on the text tool and given
现在我点击文本工具，然后给出
the percentages
百分比
to enter a group I double click on it
要进入一个组，我双击它
then I right click on the orange
然后我右击橙子
rectangle and choose select same fill
矩形，然后选择选择相同的填充
color
颜色
I press delete to delete all
我按DELETE键删除所有
placeholders
占位符
I don't need the text to be in a group
我不需要将文本放在组中
anymore so I select them all right click
所以我把它们全部选中，点击鼠标右键
and choose ungroup
并选择取消分组
finally let's place the team names I
最后，让我们把参赛队的名字
create a new layer called teams I select
创建一个名为Teams I Sect的新图层
the text tool and click on the canvas I
文本工具，然后在画布上单击I
set text alignment to left align
将文本对齐设置为左对齐
I press caps lock I type Manchester
我按下大写锁定我输入曼彻斯特
press enter and type United I select the
按Enter键并键入United I选择
text United
Text United
I hold the ALT key and with my arrow up
我按住Alt键并向上移动箭头
key adjust the spacing I click on the
按键调整间距我点击
select tool and make the text larger
选择工具并放大文本
I click on the text again so I can
我再次点击文本，这样我就可以
rotate it I duplicate the text then I
旋转它我复制文本然后我
drag to the right and with my spacebar I
向右拖动，然后使用空格键
make copies
复制一份
I double click on a copy press Ctrl a
我双击一个副本，按Ctrl a
and change the name
并更改名称
I also change the name of the other
我还把另一个的名字改了
copies
副本
I select the team names I go to align
我选择我要对齐的团队名称
and distribute behind relative 2 I
并分布在相对2 i的后面
select selection area to align the text
选择选择区域以对齐文本
I click on align top edges
我点击对齐顶端边缘
and at the top I type chance of winning
在顶端，我输入获胜的机会
or qualifying
或资格赛